eso.tv 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | TotalPsychics.com

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the users of  **TotalPsychics.com** ; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**1.) Collection of Information**

**We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:**

a.) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, operating system, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;

b.) information related to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make;

c.) information that you provide to us for the purpose of signing up with us;

d.) logs of all user activities on  **TotalPsychics.com** , including private sessions, in order to ensure the safety of Experts and the quality of the service provided to Visitors.

**2.) Cookies**

**We use cookies on this website.**  A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This   
enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

**We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.**  We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.

**Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.**  (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

**3.) Using your personal data**

**Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.**

We may use your personal information to:

a.) administer the website;

b.) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

c.) enable your use of the services available on the website;

d.) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you (Visitors) or to make payments to you (Experts);

e.) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

f.) send you e-mail notifications which you have specifically requested;

g.) send to you marketing communications which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by e-mail or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by e-mailing us);

h.) provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

i.) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

**We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties.**

**4.) Other disclosures**

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, **we may disclose information about you:**

a.) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

b.) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

c.) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention).

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**5.) Security of your personal data**

We take all reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted [using SSL technology].

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will never ask you for your password in e-mail.

**6.) Policy amendments 1**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  **You should check this page occasionally**  to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by e-mail.

**7.) Your rights**

If you have provided us with any personal information,  **you may request us to remove such information**  from our records by contacting us in e-mail at [info@totalpsychics.com](mailto:info@totalpsychics.com)

**8.) Third party websites**

The website may contain links to other websites.  **We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.**

**9.) Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**10.) Contact**

**If you have any questions**  about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by e-mail to [info@totalpsychics.com](mailto:info@totalpsychics.com)

1. Changes to the policy – in particular as to permissible uses of personal data – may not be retrospective. In other words, if you collect personal information on one basis, you cannot, simply by changing the terms of your policy, go on to legitimately use that information on a different basis.
